Based on a true story
Dauntless: The Battle of Midway is a war, action,
drama film directed by Mike Phillips.
By June 1942, the Japanese Navy has swept across the Pacific.
In an effort to change the course of the war, a United States carrier group is
positioned off the coast of Midway, tasked with springing a trap on the enemy.
During this pivotal battle, the two-man crew of a U.S.
Navy dive bomber is forced to ditch in the sea.
Set adrift, the men look towards their comrades for rescue; namely, the ragtag
crew of a PBY Catalina, who are sent to search for survivors.
Amid the vast openness of the Pacific, with days passing and the chance of
rescue fading, the men are forced to face their own mortality.
Rear Admirial Raymond Spruance, played by Judd Nelson.
Captain Miles Browning, played by C. Thomas Howell.
Doc, played by Mendel Fogelman.
Pags, played by Aidan Bristow.
Banks, played by James Austin Kerr.
Norman Vandiver, played by Jade Willey.
Dauntless: The Battle of Midway (a.k.a.
Adrift as the working title) is a 2019 action film based on a true story
of United States Navy aviators at the Battle of Midway.
The theme of the film combines war and aviation film genres.
The film was written, directed and produced by Mike Phillips.
The screenplay of Dauntless: The Battle of Midway was written by
Adam Klein and based on an original story by Phillips.
The tone is emotional.